(Sheldon(on phone):)would be perfect to appear
on our first panel.
Well, now, why are you saying "no"?
You haven't even asked him yet.
(Sheldon(on phone):)You know, excuse me,
but I sat through Iron Man 2.
(Sheldon(on phone):)I believe he owes me
two hours of his time.
(Sheldon(on phone):)They hung up on me.
(Leonard:)Did you tell them that you're
holding your convention at
(Leonard:)a Marie Callender's, and that every
panelist gets a free slice of pie?
(Sheldon:)I didn't even get to that part.
(Leonard:)Look, even your friend Wil Wheaton
thinks this is a waste of time.
(Sheldon:)Not true.
Wil thinks this is a great idea.
(Sheldon:)He was just concerned that
he wasn't a big enough celebrity
(Sheldon:)to headline such an amazing event.
(Sheldon:)Also, that's the same day
that he shampoos his beard.
Sheldon, I just don't think this
is going to come together for you.
(Sheldon:)You don't know that.
(Sheldon:)I still have plenty
of solid leads on this list.
(Leonard:)-Good luck.
-No, wait.
(Sheldon:)I need you to call Stan Lee,
Leonard Nimoy